<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Running on Marek Dlugos — Revenue Growth, Product, Design, Software Engineering.</title><link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/tags/running/</link><description>Recent content in Running on Marek Dlugos — Revenue Growth, Product, Design, Software Engineering.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 08:08:25 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.marekdlugos.com/tags/running/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>From No Running Experience to Half Marathon in Four Months</title><link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/blog/from-no-running-experience-to-half-marathon-in-just-four-months/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 08:08:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.marekdlugos.com/blog/from-no-running-experience-to-half-marathon-in-just-four-months/</guid><description>&lt;p>I was the guy who only ran in school because the PE teacher made us do it—not exactly a big fan. But I’ve always admired certain people around me for their athletic achievements. I thought those were not possible for me to achieve.&lt;/p>

 &lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
 &lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" loading="eager" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/a4MxPc0iAHU?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" title="YouTube video">&lt;/iframe>
 &lt;/div>

&lt;p>After avoiding any form of exercise for the past 2-3 years. Before, I used to basketball, do ballroom dancing, or go to the gym. The first two required others and facilities. With the gym, I just hate the fact that here in Europe it&amp;rsquo;s so rare to live in an apartment building that would have a gym. Otherwise, I just find it annoying and time-consuming to commute to the gym. Seeing a lot of my connections on socials running, I always wanted to see what and if I could achieve in this sport. Another advantage? The only thing I&amp;rsquo;d need were shoes. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter if I am currently traveling or whether there&amp;rsquo;s a facility nearby. I could just get out there and explore.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>