<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Marek Dlugos — Revenue Growth, Product, Design, Software Engineering.</title><link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Marek Dlugos — Revenue Growth, Product, Design, Software Engineering.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 08:08:25 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.marekdlugos.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>From No Running Experience to Half Marathon in Four Months</title><link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/blog/from-no-running-experience-to-half-marathon-in-just-four-months/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 08:08:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.marekdlugos.com/blog/from-no-running-experience-to-half-marathon-in-just-four-months/</guid><description>I was the guy who only ran in school because the PE teacher made us do it—not exactly a big fan. But I’ve always admired certain people around me for their athletic achievements. I thought those were not possible for me to achieve.
After avoiding any form of exercise for the past 2-3 years. Before, I used to basketball, do ballroom dancing, or go to the gym. The first two required others and facilities.</description></item><item><title>Motivation to Write</title><link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/blog/motivation-to-write/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:12:33 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.marekdlugos.com/blog/motivation-to-write/</guid><description>For many years I enjoyed reading blogs, but was never brave enough to write one myself. I found the fact that the content becomes obsolete and stuff I write won&amp;rsquo;t be true anymore (or people will disagree with me) scary. But here I am today, in the VS Code typing in the first lines of what I am hoping will help me clear my head and form my thoughts better. Become more intimate with the world and people who want to tag along.</description></item></channel></rss>