<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Marek Dlugos — Revenue Growth, Product, Design, Software Engineering.</title><link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Marek Dlugos — Revenue Growth, Product, Design, Software Engineering.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:12:33 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Motivation to Write</title><link>http://localhost:1313/blog/motivation-to-write/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:12:33 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/motivation-to-write/</guid><description>For many years I enjoyed reading blogs, but was never brave enough to write one myself. I found the fact that the content becomes obsolete and stuff I write won&amp;rsquo;t be true anymore (or people will disagree with me) scary. But here I am today, in the VS Code typing in the first lines of what I am hoping will help me clear my head and form my thoughts better. Become more intimate with the world and people who want to tag along.</description></item><item><title>1 Backpack 150 Days on the Road From Freezing Cold to Sweating</title><link>http://localhost:1313/blog/1-backpack-150-days-on-the-road-from-freezing-cold-to-sweating/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:34:41 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/1-backpack-150-days-on-the-road-from-freezing-cold-to-sweating/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s funny how when I tell people I travel for a longer period of time with one backpack only, people have a hard time to comprehend that while it seems incredibly easy to me.
A couple of years ago, I kindly asked my friends to take two of my big suitcases from South Korea to Europe for me, while I embarked on a 2 month long adventure traveling through South East Asia on my own with a tiny Shopify backpack.</description></item><item><title>I Did 4 Semesters Abroad in Different Cities Here Is the Best City</title><link>http://localhost:1313/blog/i-did-4-semesters-abroad-in-different-cities-here-is-the-best-city/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:06:23 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/i-did-4-semesters-abroad-in-different-cities-here-is-the-best-city/</guid><description/></item><item><title>How I Quit My Job and Traveled for Four Months</title><link>http://localhost:1313/blog/how-i-quit-my-job-and-traveled-for-four-months/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 22:55:31 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/how-i-quit-my-job-and-traveled-for-four-months/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>