<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Marek Dlugos — Revenue Growth, Product, Design, Software Engineering.</title><link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/</link><description>Recent content on Marek Dlugos — Revenue Growth, Product, Design, Software Engineering.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:12:33 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.marekdlugos.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Motivation to Write</title><link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/blog/motivation-to-write/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:12:33 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.marekdlugos.com/blog/motivation-to-write/</guid><description>For many years I enjoyed reading blogs, but was never brave enough to write one myself. I found the fact that the content becomes obsolete and stuff I write won&amp;rsquo;t be true anymore (or people will disagree with me) scary. But here I am today, in the VS Code typing in the first lines of what I am hoping will help me clear my head and form my thoughts better. Become more intimate with the world and people who want to tag along.</description></item><item><title>Now</title><link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 12:44:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.marekdlugos.com/now/</guid><description> Last update: July 12, 2024, from my home in Lausanne, Switzerland.
Current priorities:
Prepare and pass the Goethe-Zertifikat B2 in German. Find a new job. Move to the German speaking part of Switzerland.</description></item><item><title>Work</title><link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/work/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 20:09:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.marekdlugos.com/work/</guid><description>I used to create software. Now I am growing its potential. Leading brands trusted my work Work Experience Customer Success Manager at SpotMe Jan 2021 till Jan 2024 — Lausanne, Switzerland Managed the largest portfolio of contracts value in EMEA as a single CSM ($1.5M) at the time. Mainly a sales role. Managed strategic relationships as an IT vendor with 30+ enterprises. Coordinated with the product, operations, and engineering to ensure SLAs were met and required improvements were delivered.</description></item><item><title>Hobbies</title><link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/hobbies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 20:09:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.marekdlugos.com/hobbies/</guid><description>Traveling Countries visited: 64
Journeys around the world: 2
My Flight Radar profile
Asia Cambodia, China (Hong Kong, Macau), Indonesia, Israel, Jordan, Kuwait, Laos, Malaysia, Maldives, Palestine, Philippines, Qatar (Doha), Saudi Arabia, Singapore, South Korea, Taiwan, Thailand, Turkey, United Arab Emirates, Vietnam Europe Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, Czech Republic, Denmark, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Netherlands, Poland, Portugal, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, United Kingdom, Vatican City Latin America Argentina, Bahamas, Bolivia, Brazil, Chile, Colombia, Costa Rica, Dominican Republic, Ecuador, Mexico, Panama, Peru, Uruguay North America Canada (Ottawa, Toronto, Montreal), USA (Florida, Hawaii, NYC, Puerto Rico, SF) Sharing Interviews I was fortunate to meet a lot of very interesting people along the way and now I am happy to bring 5 interviews with some of them!</description></item><item><title>Sharing</title><link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/sharing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 12:44:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.marekdlugos.com/sharing/</guid><description>Follow along LinkedIn Work related content together with my resume. Facebook Life updates and insights. Instagram Travels. Twitter Tech related content. Startups and web development. YouTube Travel vlogs and interviews. Medium Long-read stories. Dribbble Design projects. Github Code projects. Writing Life Stories Feb 2023
Saudi Arabia - everything you need to know
Dec 2019
Today is My Sister’s Second Birthday Since She Died
Jun 2017
My Experience as a Shopify Intern, And Why You Should Go For It, Too</description></item><item><title>Side Projects</title><link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/side-projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 18:32:06 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.marekdlugos.com/side-projects/</guid><description>I am driven by improving things around me. Take Me as an Intern 2016 During the 4 months gap between graduating high school and starting of university I wanted to be an intern so I made one-page site describing my skills and how can I contribute to the business. The site made it as #1 on YC Hacker News. Had over 30k visitors in one night and get huge media attention all around the world.</description></item><item><title>Education &amp; Awards</title><link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/education-awards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 18:05:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.marekdlugos.com/education-awards/</guid><description>Education The Story High-quality technical education abroad has been my aim for a long time, which is why I left my home country after graduating from the best tech high school in Slovakia (according to the INEKO ranking).
Followed by applying for the Ivy League universities. The University of Cambridge, according to rankings, the 4th best university in the world, invited me for interviews where I exceeded their expectations in Computer Science but didn't persuade them with my math skills.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/podcast/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.marekdlugos.com/podcast/</guid><description>&lt;!doctype html> Marek Dlugoš Podcast Rozhovory Marek Dlugoš Môj osobný web Väčšinou na internete vystupujem v angličtine, no teraz som sa to rozhodol oživiť a preto prinášam rozhovory s mojimi kamarátmi na startup témy. Rád by som Ťa spoznal, keď si si dal tú námahu nájsť tento web. Zanechaj mi pár údajov a ja Ti napíšem vždy, keď budem mať niečo nové a zaujímavé. Meno E-mail Web / Instagram / Facebook Čo stojí za úspechom akéhokoľvek projektu?</description></item></channel></rss>