<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marek Dlugos on Marek Dlugos — Revenue Growth, Product, Design, Software Engineering.</title>
    <link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marek Dlugos on Marek Dlugos — Revenue Growth, Product, Design, Software Engineering.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 18:05:30 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.marekdlugos.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Work</title>
      <link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 20:09:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marekdlugos.com/work/</guid>
      <description>I used to create software. Now I am selling it.  Skills Business-wise  Account Expansion Demand Generation   Technology-wise  Account Expansion Demand Generation      I can help you with Business-wise  Account Expansion Demand Generation   Technology-wise  Account Expansion Demand Generation     --  Work Experience Account Executive at SpotMe Dec 2019 till now — Lausanne, Switzerland Product Designer at Price f(x) May 2017 till Jan 2019 – Prague, Czech Republic Increased sales at various enterprises through dynamic pricing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hobbies</title>
      <link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/hobbies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 20:09:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marekdlugos.com/hobbies/</guid>
      <description>Traveling Countries visited: 46
 Journeys around the world: 2
 My Flight Radar profile
      var map = AmCharts.makeChart(&#34;mapdiv&#34;, { type: &#34;map&#34;, theme: &#34;dark&#34;, projection: &#34;mercator&#34;, panEventsEnabled: true, backgroundColor: &#34;#535364&#34;, backgroundAlpha: 1, zoomControl: { zoomControlEnabled: true }, dataProvider: { map: &#34;worldHigh&#34;, getAreasFromMap: true, areas: [ { &#34;id&#34;: &#34;AT&#34;, &#34;showAsSelected&#34;: true }, { &#34;id&#34;: &#34;BE&#34;, &#34;showAsSelected&#34;: true }, { &#34;id&#34;: &#34;BG&#34;, &#34;showAsSelected&#34;: true }, { &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing</title>
      <link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 12:44:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marekdlugos.com/sharing/</guid>
      <description>Follow along LinkedIn Work related content together with my resume.  Facebook Life updates and insights.  Instagram Travels.  Twitter Tech related content. Startups and web development.  YouTube Travel vlogs and interviews.  Medium Long-read stories.  Dribbble Design projects.  Github Code projects.     Writing Life Stories  Dec 2019
 Today is My Sister’s Second Birthday Since She Died
  Jun 2017</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Side Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/side-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 18:32:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marekdlugos.com/side-projects/</guid>
      <description>I am driven by improving things around me.   Take Me as an Intern Jun 2016 — Oct 2016 During the 4 months gap between graduating high school and starting of university I wanted to be an intern so I made one-page site describing my skills and how can I contribute to the business. The site made it as #1 on YC Hacker News. Had over 30k visitors in one night and get huge media attention all around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education Awards</title>
      <link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/education-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 18:05:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marekdlugos.com/education-awards/</guid>
      <description>Education The Story  High-quality technical education abroad has been my aim for a long time, which is why I left my home country after graduating from the best tech high school in Slovakia (according to the INEKO ranking).
Followed by applying for the Ivy League universities. The University of Cambridge, according to rankings, the 4th best university in the world, invited me for interviews where I exceeded their expectations in Computer Science but didn&#39;t persuade them with my math skills.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>