<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Support on Marek Dlugos — Revenue Growth, Product, Design, Software Engineering.</title><link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/tags/support/</link><description>Recent content in Support on Marek Dlugos — Revenue Growth, Product, Design, Software Engineering.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 19:12:33 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.marekdlugos.com/tags/support/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>It bothers me how little startups care about 360 customer view</title><link>https://www.marekdlugos.com/blog/it-bothers-me-how-little-startups-care-about-360-customer-view/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 19:12:33 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.marekdlugos.com/blog/it-bothers-me-how-little-startups-care-about-360-customer-view/</guid><description>&lt;p>If you worked in sales before, you know you can&amp;rsquo;t get far without a well set customer relationships management software (a.k.a CRM). If you have not worked in sales before, here&amp;rsquo;s my short essay on why this is something you want to invest in straight from the beginning.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Ensuring you have the right foundations is what you can benefit from largely later.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="why-should-i-even-care">Why should I even care?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Perhaps, you are a small team, but whether you want it or not (hopefully you want it) you have to communicate with (potential) customers, investors, and partners. The requirements to do this well grow quickly - first you want to start tracking the list of potential conversations you had, then you want to track the number of people who signed up for your free trial/tier, then you need to email them to let reengage them. Lastly, when they reach out to you, ideally you want to be able to keep track of that too.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>